B. John Hunter

1740 Love Lee Road Morgantown, KY 42261 270-421-7920 | B.JohnHunter71@gmail.com https://venatro71.github.io/Portfolio/ http://twitter.com/@jhunterwebdev www.linkedin.com/in/john-hunter-9b90b035

PROFILE

Computer technician with 10+ years experience. Energetic problem solver. Effective in a team or independent environment. Highly Organized and detail oriented. Seeking an environment where I can best utilize my skills and develop new ones.

SKILLS

- Solid understanding of Windows 3.11 11, MacOS.
- Advanced troubleshooting skills
- Intermediate networking skills
- Intermediate Linux OS skills

WORK EXPERIENCE

Premier Pilot Cars, Morgantown, KY

September 2017 - September 2019

Operator/Owner

- Escort oversize loads from factory to job site
- Loading and unloading of oversize steel beams.
- Traffic control
- Steering of rear dolly to safely maneuver beam through traffic and to final unloading position.

Computers Plus, Bowling Green, KY

October 2007 - February 2009

Service Manager/Technician

- Responsible for all repairs, upgrades and service process in service dept.
- Development and implementation of service procedures.
- Training of store personnel in service related issues and process
- Direct customer relations for both sales and service.
- Inventory management

AAA Systems, Bowling Green, KY

June 2001 - September 2003

Service Technician/ Installer

- Installation and service of: residential and commercial security and fire systems, access control systems, CCTV systems.
- Supervised crews and trained new employees.
- Direct customer relations

EDUCATION

ITT Technical College, San Diego, Ca

Sept 1991 - Jun 1993

Electronics Engineering

Studied electrical circuit design

Commonwealth Coders

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Web Development

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React
- Python